var questions =[{"question":"hazard perception means","answers":["nothing","expect anything","anticipation of what is in front of you"],"correctAnswer":"2"},{"question":"hazards are used","answers":["to warn vehicles ahead","when slowing down","to warn vehicles behind"],"correctAnswer":"2"},{"question":"how many passengers are allowed in a learner drive vehicle","answers":["0","2","1"],"correctAnswer":"2"},{"question":"in which class is a laybye sign","answers":["regulatory","danger warning","informative"],"correctAnswer":"2"},{"question":"the amber sequence of a robot insists that","answers":["give way to traffic from the right","give way to traffic from the right","wait to cross if it safe to do so"],"correctAnswer":"2"},{"question":"diverging lanes means","answers":["2 lanes become one","1 lane becomes 2","lane is going to broaden"],"correctAnswer":"1"},{"question":"if the engine engine of a motor cycle exceed 350 centimetre sqaures what must be fitted to the motor cycle","answers":["proper pillion seat","crash bars","foot rest"],"correctAnswer":"1"},{"question":"in an emergency ","answers":["hoot","stop at once","reduce speed"],"correctAnswer":"1"},{"question":"in which class is a valesolex driver","answers":["1","3","5"],"correctAnswer":"1"},{"question":"is a 10 year old allowed in the luggage compartment of a truck","answers":["depends with the behaviour of the childe","no","yes"],"correctAnswer":"1"},{"question":"lane changing proceedure","answers":["signal and turn","rear view mirror check, signal, blind spot check, hand signal","check mirrors, signal and turn"],"correctAnswer":"1"},{"question":"never should you turn right","answers":["when slowing down","in front of oncoming traffic","none of the above"],"correctAnswer":"1"},{"question":"road markings with transverse lines","answers":["are carriageway markings","have  a regulatory effect","are danger warning"],"correctAnswer":"1"},{"question":"switch on lights between","answers":["1730 and 0630","1700 and 0600","when it is necessary to do so"],"correctAnswer":"1"},{"question":"direction signs are ","answers":["informative","regulatory","danger warning"],"correctAnswer":"0"},{"question":"direction signs used in conjuction with prohibition lines ","answers":["have a regulatory effect","are informative","are danger warning"],"correctAnswer":"0"},{"question":"flashing amber with a red rectangular sign ","answers":["emphasizes the existence of danger","a train passing ahead","stop "],"correctAnswer":"0"},{"question":"hand brake is used","answers":["to keep the vehicle stationery","to keep the vehicle stationery on a steep road",""],"correctAnswer":"0"},{"question":"how far behind a broken down motor vehicle do you place a reflective triangle","answers":["30-50m","50-80m","10-30m"],"correctAnswer":"0"},{"question":"if you see an accident ","answers":["slow down and drive cautiosly","do not panick","stop and go report to the police"],"correctAnswer":"0"},{"question":"in rural areas give way to traffic","answers":["that enters the junction before you","to traffic from the right","to traffic from the left"],"correctAnswer":"0"},{"question":"motorcycles travel in the ","answers":["left lane","right lane","any lane"],"correctAnswer":"0"},{"question":"one way sign is","answers":["informative","danger warning","regulatory"],"correctAnswer":"0"},{"question":"to dry off brakes after passing through deep waters ","answers":["move slowly whilst gently applying brakes","acceralate rapidly ","wait till they are dry"],"correctAnswer":"0"},{"question":"to keep a vehicle stationery you use","answers":["parking brake","foot brake","neutral gear"],"correctAnswer":"0"}];